(Penny:)and we promise
we'll leave you alone.
(Amy:)Fine. Um...
(Amy:)he's British.
(both squeal)
(chuckling):
All right, that is a juicy one.
(Penny:)All right, where is
Tall British Dave taking you?
(Bernadette:)Tea and basketball?
(Amy:)To that new Italian place
on Walnut.
(Bernadette:)Oh, nice.
(Amy:)I'm gonna go look for other shoes.
Good luck.
(Penny:)I threw out all my tall ones
when I married Leonard.
(Bernadette:)Hey, you want
(Bernadette:)to swing by that place tonight
and get a look at this guy?
(Penny:)We don't even know what time
they're gonna be there.
(Bernadette:)I'll just call the restaurant,
(Bernadette:)pretend I'm Amy
and check the reservation.
(Penny:)Damn, you're sneaky.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, but I'm little,
so it's adorable.
(Howard:)I think the quickest way
to find you a new girlfriend
(Howard:)is just to get you on every
dating Web site out there.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
(Sheldon:)I've heard that on those
sites, often when you think
(Sheldon:)you're corresponding with someone,
it's actually a computer program
(Sheldon:)pretending to be
a real person.
(Raj:)And you're afraid
it'll do a better job than you?